irsc.edu 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy - Indian River State College

Indian River State College is committed to protecting your privacy. The following privacy notice describes what information we collect from you when you visit [www.irsc.edu](https://www.irsc.edu/ "www.irsc.edu") and how we use this information. Read this privacy notice carefully so that you understand our privacy practices. 

The privacy notice was last revised on November 14, 2018.

## Indian River State College Internet Privacy Policy

Your privacy is paramount. Simply stated, our policy is to share no personal information about you when you visit our website, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. 

#### Information We Gather/Log Data

When you visit this website, our web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in identification of your personal email address or other personal information. In addition, we gather information regarding the volume and timing of access to our website by collecting information on the date, time and website pages accessed by our visitors. Your session will be tracked, but you will remain anonymous as a user. 

This data is used in conjunction with Google Analytics to gather metrics on site usage, including geographic location of visitors and pathways navigated through the website. As part of Google Analytics, we also gather device and browser-related information. We do this so we can improve the content of our website, and this information is not shared with other organizations. Again, only aggregate information is collected and individual visitor's personal information is not identified. 

#### Information You May Provide

If you choose to share personal information with us—by sending a message or filling out an electronic form with personal information—we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period of time, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies unless required or authorized to do so by state or federal law. 

#### Collection and Use of Email Addresses

Under Florida law, email addresses are public records. If you do not want your email address released in response to a public records request, do not send electronic mail to this entity. Instead, contact the College by phone or in writing. 

## Cookies

Cookies are text files stored on your computer and accessible only to the websites which create them. Our website may use first-party cookies to keep you logged into secure areas of the website and/or to keep track of your preferences as you interact with certain services. We may also employ third-party cookies that enable third-party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g., advertising, interactive content and analytics). These cookies collect information that is used either in identifiable or aggregate form to help us understand how our website is being used and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. The parties that set these third-party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits this website and also when it visits certain other websites. You may disable cookies in your browser; however, our website may not work properly if you do so. 

#### Social Networking Cookies

If you share our content through social media, such as liking us on Facebook or tweeting about us on Twitter, those social networks will record that you have done so and may set a cookie for this purpose. If you wish to opt-out of any of these social interactions, refer to the specific social media platform for instructions on how to do so. 

## External Website Links

From time-to-time, we will link to external websites that we neither own nor control. Indian River State College is not responsible for the content, privacy practices or web accessibility needs on these websites. 

## Protecting Your Information

No method of transmitting over the internet or storing electronic data is 100% secure, but this site has measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information that is under our control. We have dedicated information security programs and work hard to continuously enhance our technical and operational security measures. 

## Contact Us

IRSC reserves the right to change this privacy policy without notice. Questions about this privacy notice or the privacy practices it describes, should be directed to [info@irsc.edu](mailto:info@irsc.edu?subject=).
